export const flashCardData = [
    { front: "1+1", back: "2", timesShown: 0, correctlyAnswered: 0, accuracy: 0, familiarity: "NEW" },
    { front: "1+2", back: "3", timesShown: 0, correctlyAnswered: 0, accuracy: 0, familiarity: "NEW" },
    { front: "1+3", back: "4", timesShown: 0, correctlyAnswered: 0, accuracy: 0, familiarity: "NEW" },
    { front: "1+4", back: "5", timesShown: 0, correctlyAnswered: 0, accuracy: 0, familiarity: "NEW" },
    { front: "1+5", back: "6", timesShown: 0, correctlyAnswered: 0, accuracy: 0, familiarity: "NEW" }

];

export const multCardData = [
    { front: "1x1", back: "1", timesShown: 0, correctlyAnswered: 0, accuracy: 0, familiarity: "NEW" },
    { front: "1x2", back: "2", timesShown: 0, correctlyAnswered: 0, accuracy: 0, familiarity: "NEW" },
    { front: "1x3", back: "3", timesShown: 0, correctlyAnswered: 0, accuracy: 0, familiarity: "NEW" },
    { front: "1x4", back: "4", timesShown: 0, correctlyAnswered: 0, accuracy: 0, familiarity: "NEW" },
    { front: "1x5", back: "5", timesShown: 0, correctlyAnswered: 0, accuracy: 0, familiarity: "NEW" }

];

export const vocabData = [
    { front: "baloo", back: "a bear", timesShown: 0, correctlyAnswered: 0, accuracy: 0, familiarity: "NEW" },
    { front: "nadir", back: "lowest point", timesShown: 0, correctlyAnswered: 0, accuracy: 0, familiarity: "NEW" },
    { front: "zenith", back: "highest point", timesShown: 0, correctlyAnswered: 0, accuracy: 0, familiarity: "NEW" },
    { front: "abdicate", back: "give up the throne", timesShown: 0, correctlyAnswered: 0, accuracy: 0, familiarity: "NEW" },
    { front: "caustic", back: "acidic", timesShown: 0, correctlyAnswered: 0, accuracy: 0, familiarity: "NEW" }

];

 

 